

CONTACT

https://aideisayevaa.github.io/ Portfolio/my-portolio/

in www.linkedin.com/in/aidaisayeva

(+994 51 332 60 23

isayevaa868@gmail.com

https://github.com/aideisayevaa

💡 Baku, Azerbaijan

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Azerbaijan - Native

English - Pre-intermediate

Turkish - Fluent

Russian - Conversational

SKILLS

HTML _____

CSS

SASS

Bootstrap

JavaScript •

Git

Github

React

Figma

AIDA ISAYEVA

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I am Aida Isayeva

I am a 4th year Computer Science student of the Academy of Public Administration under the President. I have been studying and working in the field of programming for 2 years. I learn new knowledge and skills every day. I am improving myself every day. My interest in programming is increasing day by day.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Lima Technology Center - Front-end Developer

November 2021 - January 2022

- · Coding website with team
- · Using Html Css Javascript technologies
- Coding responsive website
- Analyzing and debugging the website

Pragmatech Education and Development Center - Front-end Mentor

September 2021 - November 2021

- Answering students' questions
- Giving assignments to students
- Helping students create Github accounts

EDUCATION

Academy of Public Administration under the President - Computer Science

September 2019 - June 2023

Coders Azerbaijan

August 2022 - now

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Google searching
- Problem solving
- Organisational capacity
- Operability and commitment
- Resistance to stress
- Team work
- Activity